Okay, we are going to call the order today's meeting of the Miami Special Utility Authority.
I didn't do this indication by pastor. First of all, I have this church reform plan.
We're going to have to be in here.
Let's pray again.
Father, it's always such an honor and privilege to pray for our city and pray for city leaders and deaf.
I just pray that you and it's like enough their business tonight that you would just give them wisdom and all the decisions that they have to make that it's the best thing for our city to do.
So Father, just as you were tells us, we just asked for wisdom.
That's what we do on there by half tonight.
Thank you to this time of the year.
What a great time of the year it is.
And for the most of all, thank you that it reminds us that you sent your son to God across for us.
And so the little baby born in the land, you know, we always remember that.
That's what the season is.
Please Father, that's what we ask you to do.
Amen.
First of all, I'm going to pledge.
I pledge allegiance to God.
I'm going to the United States of America.
It's a military pilot for which it stands.
One nation, another God.
And it is full of liberty and justice for all.
Thank you.
To be seated.
You can add a number of four.
There's public internet and unscheduled personal temperatures.
And then when the audience is watching the dress, you can tell when you're going to go read.
On any agenda items.
I don't find the consent agenda staff is asking for item six and seven, which are the claims and minutes to be on the consent agenda.
There are no questions or any kind of motion.
Let me give it a minute.
Any second?
Second.
Go call.
The Johnson.
Lewis.
I chose.
Paul pressure there on us.
Either way.
Also in June and next year, we're going to work for a number of times.
Excuse me.
17,5, 18,6.
Not to see the 168,700.
Alicia.
And Sean.
Are you Sean?
Good.
What are you going to talk to us about tonight?
So this work order is for the mainstream street state thing.
Right?
So basically we're going to continue to figure out how mainstream through the plans.
And we're going to put that up for street.
So sidewalk, dirt, gutter, pavement, for place and litter.
And we'll fix that water line.
That's a little street too.
And this is on the south side of central.
Right?
This is north.
This will be in first.
In first, we'll go west between first and fourth.
Yeah.
So wherever tracks.
Okay.
Two.
Yep.
So the remaining city piece of mainstream.
Okay.
Which will include the drainage.
Yes.
So we're probably looking at something about re-grading there.
First North West in front of Coleman.
Okay.
Get that water to wrap around like we talked about earlier in the year.
And the survey that they had done before is saving us some money on this they will be using that so they're not going to be doing anything that they already done.
And do we have a timeline?
Gold would be mid-late summer bid.
Okay?
Have a bit back at Gretty then.
So hopefully we can catch Randy in the construction season.
So actually start in late summer hopefully.
That's the hope or fall.
Okay.
Any other questions on this particular agenda item?
I think do we have a motion to approve?
I'll make a motion.
And I'll second that roll call please.
Lewis, I've chosen.
Johnson.
Okay.
I have to make a new business and a new business dean or anyone?
No, you're right.
Staff are portraying your packet.
I've been 11 is community announcements and the announcements to make.
No, this one might.
Next one.
And out of the problems we've done.
I'll make a motion to adjourn.
Do we have a second?
Okay.
Go for it.